JOSEPH HARRISON

Self-taught Web Developer

Joescript.io

INFO

PHONE

07427113200

FMATI

joe@joescript.io

PORTFOLIO

joescript.io

SKILLS

JavaScript, CSS & html.

React, node.js & Redux.

Express.js & PostgreSQL

HOBBIES

I love to spend my evenings and weekends climbing rocks, preferably in Fontainebleau, France with fresh pastries, good cheese and great wine. I also like to make handcrafted furniture, most recently I made a sofa bed and alcove cabinets and shelves.

EDUCATION

ZERO TO MASTERY

Complete web developer in 2021 completion

GCSE's, WoodBridge High School

Sep 2005 — Jul 2010 Finished GCSE's with:

- 3 A's in Science, Maths and Statistics
- 2 B's in English and science (pt2).
- 5 other courses

PROFILE

Being furloughed gave me the chance to learn. I spent this time making all manner of things, starting with lots of carpentry projects and then moving on to web development. I started with Html, CSS and JavaScript, learning as much as I could just from free resources online. Then I took the course "The complete web developer: Zero to Mastery" and that is where my newfound love for development began. Since then, I have been tirelessly learning all I can, focusing on JavaScript and React. I may not be the most experienced developer out there but my drive to better myself and my other skills gained in the catering sector mean I will work the hardest for this opportunity.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Operations Manager, Street Confit

London

Jul 2017 - Present

- Developed and pitched plan for innovative product development.
- Evaluated suppliers by assessing quality, timeliness and compliance of deliveries to maintain tight cost controls and maximize business operational efficiency.
 - Managed daily operations of organization, orchestrating forward-thinking strategies to accomplish profit and expansion goals.
 - Partnered with vendors and suppliers to effectively manage and budget while keeping overheads low.

General Manager, Hola Paella

London

Feb 2015 — Aug 2017

- Managing day to day running of the shop, including licensing, health and safety and staff management.
- Creation of new products and new business.
- Developed value-added solutions and approaches by leveraging trends in customer marketplaces and industries.
- Maximized efficiency by coaching and mentoring a small team on fast food principles, industry practices, company procedures and internal accounting system.

Sales Assistant - Supervisor, Hola Paella

London

Feb 2010 — Feb 2015

- Assisted customers with prompt and polite support in-person.
- Maintained records related to sales, returns and inventory availability.
- Collaborated with managers to provide customer feedback andrecommend operational changes to meet emerging trends.
- Drove team revenue totals by bringing in over £200k in sales.